Interviewer: Do you think you have a healthy diet?
Graziella: Um, for the most part, I would say I have a healthy diet.
Er, lots of fruits and vegetables, and a little bit of chocolate, here and there.
Interviewer: How much sugar and salt do you eat?
Graziella: Um, I don’t have that much salt in my diet, but with all of the fruit that I have,
I would say I have quite a bit of sugar, natural sugars.
Interviewer: Do you like cooking?
Kara: I love to cook.
Interviewer: Do you think you’re a good cook?
Kara: I do think I’m a good cook.
Interviewer: What’s your speciality?
Kara: Um, my husband is Cuban, so I learned to cook Cuban food for him, so that’s my speciality.
Interviewer: What’s the most beautiful city you’ve ever been to? Why?
Maura: Er, that’s a difficult question, but I think I’d have to say Edinburgh.
Um, it’s very beautiful, it’s got the sea, it’s got an extinct volcano in the centre, and every street has, er, a different view.
Interviewer: Where are you going to go for your next holiday?
Kevin: Er, we’ve booked that for January and we’re going to Thailand for two weeks.
Interviewer: Where are you going to stay?
Kevin: We’re staying three nights in Bangkok, three nights in an island called Ko Samui,
and five nights in an island called Ko Tao.
Interviewer: How are you going to get there?
Kevin: We are flying from Edinburgh to, er, Dubai, Dubai to Bangkok,
and then it’s another flight from Bangkok to Ko Samui, and then a ferry from Ko Samui to Ko Tao.
Interviewer: What’s the biggest difference between the US and the UK?
Mica: Um, so the biggest difference between the US and the UK in New York City,
er, food’s very different here compared to the UK. Um, lots of burgers and pizza, and fast food and things like that.